Stephanie Dunn

University of St Andrews • (0)7490 498499 • steph.k.dunn@gmail.com

Summary

I am here to ensure that your users are happy and well-fed on content. I care deeply about the user experience and I seek employment in product management, UI or UX. I am currently participating in an intensive Masters programme in Human Computer Interaction – and I've never felt more at home. I have the creative, detail oriented, forward thinking orientation necessary to make difference as a member of any team.

Computer languages: CSS, HTML, JS, Java, C++, MATLAB

Platforms: Linux, Android Studio, Eclipse, Notepad++, Adobe CS, Sketch

Education

MSc, Computer Science: Human Computer Interaction

University of St Andrews Expected Graduation: Sep 2016

BS, Cognitive Science with Specialization in Computing

University of California, Los Angeles 2009–2012

Abroad Education: Informatics

University of Edinburgh Fall 2011

Employment

SENIOR USER OPERATIONS ASSOCIATE

YELP, INC, San Francisco, California

Mar 2013 - Aug 2015

- · Detected fraud in various facets of user activity
- · Evaluated and built policy on website content
- Monitored the Sales team to ensure accountability

SOFTWARE SPECIALIST

DIGITAL WAYBILL, Santa Monica, California

Oct 2012- Mar 2013

- Supported over 300 clients with technical needs
- Assisted client software setups with database building and converting in Access
- Set up clientele partner websites

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS (MIS) INTERN

J2 GLOBAL COMMUNICATIONS, Hollywood, California

June 2012 - Oct 2012

- Performed internal technical support at the corporate headquarters
- · Imaged computers and updated necessary hardware components
- · Maintained and organized the company asset database

INTERN

SOCIAL JUSTICE LEARNING INSTITUTE, Inglewood, California

Summer 2011

· Conducted policy research, compiled data, and assisted with program implementation

Research

RESEARCH APPRENTICE

KELLMAN PERCEPTUAL LEARNING LAB, Los Angeles, California

2012

- Researching learning methods through computer simulation
- Enrolling and running participants
- · Data entry and analysis